Guide to the Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection RG.026
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Academics
  - Subseries B: Scholarships and Awards
    - Promise Fund Scholars Fall 2003, 2003 November; cuid273 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Fall 2004, 2004 October 13; cuid274 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Spring 2005, 2005 March 7; cuid275 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Spring 2005, 2005 May 9; cuid276 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Fall 2006, 2006 September; cuid277 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Spring 2006, 2006 Spring; cuid278 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Spring 2006, 2006 March; cuid279 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - George Schillinger Award 2001, 2001 October 15; cuid280 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Scholarship Party, 1966-1968; cuid281 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Sekimoto Award 1998, 1998 October 13; cuid282 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Paul & Daisy Soros Fellowship 1998, cuid283 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Ticona Awards 1998, cuid284 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Ticona Awards 1999, 1999 June; cuid285 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ticona Awards 2000, cuid286 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Unified Honors Program (BS/MS) Chemistry, undated; cuid287 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Unified Honors Program (BS/MS) Physics, undated; cuid288 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Women's Scholarship Party, 1968; cuid289 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Subseries C: Outreach Programs
    Biographical / Historical
    Youth in Engineering and Sciences (Y.E.S.) was launched by Polytechnic University with the aim of fostering a love of math and science in high school students. It began programs such as New York City Science and Technology Forum, the Future Cities Regional Competition, Future of Telecommunications Symposia, and the Women in Technology Conference.
    - Y.E.S. Center 1989, cuid290 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Y.E.S. 1996, cuid291 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Y.E.S. 1997, 1997 October; cuid292 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Y.E.S. 1998, 1998 October; cuid293 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Y.E.S. 1999, 1999 October; cuid294 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Y.E.S. 2000, 2000 October 5; cuid295 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Y.E.S. 2001, 2001 October; cuid296 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Y.E.S. 2002, 2002 October; cuid297 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Y.E.S. 2003, 2003 October; cuid298 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Y.E.S. 2005, 2005 October; cuid299 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Y.E.S. undated, cuid300 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Y.E.S. undated, cuid301 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Future City Competition 1998, 1998 January 24; cuid302 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Future City Competition 1999, 1999 January; cuid303 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Future City Competition 2000, 2000 January; cuid304 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Future City Competition 2002, 2002 January 26; cuid305 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Subseries D: Faculty Events, 1930s - 1950s
    - Emeritus Faculty, undated; cuid306 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Outreach, 1997; cuid307 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Reception, 1996; cuid308 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Development Retreat, 1998; cuid309 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Teaching Workshop, 1997; cuid310 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - New Faculty Reception, 1999 October 26; cuid311 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Series III: Administration
  - Subseries A: Poly seals
    - Poly Seals, 1932-1954; cuid312 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Polytechnic Wedgewood Plates, undated; cuid313 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Administrative Offices
    - Business Office, undated; cuid314 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Instructors Club, 1909; cuid315 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Library, 2002 August; cuid316 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Mailroom, 2008 March; cuid317 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Health Center, 2003 March; cuid318 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Special Services, undated; cuid319 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - University Relations, undated; cuid320 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Westchester Advisory Board, undated; cuid321 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Mergers and Agreements
    - Kingsborough and Poly Agreement Signing, 1998 August 27; cuid322 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - NYU School of Engineering and Sciences/Polytechnic Merger 1973, cuid323 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Polytechnic/NYU Merger, 2008; cuid324 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - SUNY Downstate-Poly Alliance, 2001; cuid325 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Union Signing, 1996 November; cuid326 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Subseries D: Polytechnic Board, Corporation, and Trustees
    - Annual Board of Directors Meeting, 1952; cuid327 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Board Meeting, 2003 May; cuid328 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Board of Trustees, undated; cuid329 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Board of Trustees Corporation, undated; cuid330 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Corporation Executive Committee Meeting, undated; cuid331 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Fellows, undated; cuid332 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Subseries E: Fundraising
    - APO Blood Drive, 2002 September; cuid333 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Campaign Dinner, 2001 November 27; cuid334 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Capital Campaign Kickoff, 1997 May; cuid335 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Capital Campaign Kickoff, 1997 May; cuid336 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Deferred Giving, undated; cuid337 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Fundraising- various, 1950s, 1980s; cuid338 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Honor Roll of Donors 1995-1996, cuid339 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Honor Roll of Donors 1996, cuid340 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Honor Roll of Donors 1996-1997, cuid341 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Honor Roll of Donors 1997-1998, cuid342 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Phone-A-Thon 1985, cuid343 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Phone-A-Thon 1989, cuid344 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Phone-A-Thon 1994, cuid345 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Phone-A-Thon 1995, cuid346 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Phone-A-Thon 1996, cuid347 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Phone-A-Thon 2002, cuid348 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Telephone Appeal 1960, 1960 April; cuid349 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Telephone Appeal 1961, 1961 April; cuid350 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Telephone Appeal 1962, 1962 November; cuid351 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Telephone Appeal 1966 Spring, 1966 February 28 - March 1; cuid352 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Telephone Appeal 1966 Fall, 1966 November 28-29; cuid353 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Washington Council Fund, circa 1995; cuid354 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Series IV: Publications and Productions
  - Brochure, 1994; cuid355 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Cable, 1998 Summer; cuid356 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Calendar, 1965-1967; cuid357 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - General Year Book Pictures, undated; cuid358 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, undated; cuid359 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Named Giving Brochure Images (Polytechnic exteriors and interiors), 1990s; cuid360 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - News @ Poly, 1996; cuid361 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Poly Fund Brochure, 1996; cuid362 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Poly Home Page- Jacobs Building, 1996; cuid363 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Poly in the News, undated; cuid364 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Poly Men- July 1961, 1961 July; cuid365 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Poly Men- November 1961, 1961 November; cuid366 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Poly Men- April 1962, 1962 April; cuid367 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Poly Men- July 1962, 1962 July; cuid368 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Poly Men- April 1963, 1963 April; cuid369 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Poly Men- July 1963, 1963 July; cuid370 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Poly Men- February 1964, 1964 February; cuid371 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Poly Men- September 1964, 1964 September; cuid372 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Poly Men- September 1965, 1965 September; cuid373 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Poly Men- November 1965, 1965 November; cuid374 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Poly Men- September 1966, 1966 September; cuid375 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Poly Men- November 1966, 1966 November; cuid376 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Poly Men- March 1967, 1967 March; cuid377 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Poly Men- November 1968, 1968 November; cuid378 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Poly Men- March 1969, 1969 March; cuid379 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Poly Men- May 1969, 1969 May; cuid380 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Poly Men- September 1969, 1969 September; cuid381 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Poly Men- April 1970, 1970 April; cuid382 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Polycable/Polygraphs- June-July 1975, 1975 June-July; cuid383 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Polycable/Polygraphs- September 1975, 1975 September; cuid384 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Polycable/Polygraphs- November 1975, 1975 November; cuid385 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Polycable/Polygraphs- June 1985, 1985 June; cuid386 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Polytechnic Reporter, undated; cuid387 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - President's Associates Brochure, 1998; cuid388 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - President's Report Photos, 1987-1988; cuid389 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - President's Report 1994-1997, cuid390 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - President's Report 1997-1998, cuid391 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Pride is Building Video Negatives and Stills, 1992; cuid392 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Publications, 1985; cuid393 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Sketches & Typeface for Poly Publications, 1930-1950; cuid394 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Scientific Minute, undated; cuid395 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Student Publications, Undated; cuid396 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - The Polytechnic editorial board, 1903; cuid397 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Series V: Student Life
  - Subseries A: Athletics
    - Aerobics Class, undated; cuid398 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Alumni Basketball, 1939-1990; cuid399 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Alumni Varsity Night, 1961; cuid400 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Athletic Coaches, undated; cuid401 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Athletic Trophy Awards, 1954-1957; cuid402 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Baseball, 1980-1998; cuid403 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Basketball, 1942-1977; cuid404 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Basketball, 1933-1998; cuid405 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Basketball, 1925 - 1980s; cuid406 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Boxing, undated; cuid407 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Cheerleading, undated; cuid408 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Fencing, 1952-1971; cuid409 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Football, 1886-1900; cuid410 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Gym Class and Trainers, 1941-1953; cuid411 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Judo, 1950-1998; cuid412 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Lacrosse, 1985-1994; cuid413 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Athletics, 1900s - 1980s; cuid414 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Rifle Team, 1930s -1950s; cuid415 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Soccer, 1984-1997; cuid416 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Swimming, Diving, and Water Polo, 1955-1972; cuid417 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Table Tennis, 2001 February; cuid418 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Tennis (Men), 1955-1998; cuid419 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Tennis (Women), 2005-2006; cuid420 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Track, Field & Cross Country, 1941-1997; cuid421 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Volleyball (Men), 1996-2005; cuid422 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Volleyball (Women), 1987-2004; cuid423 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Wrestling, 1926-1957; cuid424 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Subseries B: Student Life
    - 123 Campaign Kickoff, 2001 September 04; cuid425 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - African Heritage Celebration, 1998; cuid426 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Career Day Reception, undated; cuid427 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Career Fair 1997, 1997 October 26; cuid428 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Career Fair 1998, 1998 October 23; cuid429 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Career Fair 1999, 1999 November 3; cuid430 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Career Fair 1999 (Long Island), 1999 March 24; cuid431 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Career Fair 2000, 2000 October 18; cuid432 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Career Fair 2002, 2002 October; cuid433 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Chemistry Demonstration for Elementary Students, undated; cuid434 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1878, cuid435 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Class of 1879, cuid436 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Class of 1887, cuid437 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Class of 1889, cuid438 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1929, cuid439 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Class of 1930, cuid440 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Class of 1931, cuid441 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Class of 1932, cuid442 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Class of 1936, cuid443 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Class of 1963, cuid444 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Class Photos- Miscellaneous, undated; cuid445 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - College Bowl, 1963; cuid446 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Dress for Success Event, 1997 October 10; cuid447 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Engineering Trip, 1915 April 1-11; cuid448 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Fall Dance, 1967 October 28; cuid449 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Field Day, undated; cuid450 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Homecoming 1967, 1967 April 29; cuid451 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Homecoming 1968, 1968 May 4; cuid452 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Homecoming/Freshman Roundup 1970, cuid453 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Homecoming/Freshman Roundup 1971, cuid454 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Homecoming 2003, cuid455 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Homecoming 2004, 2004 November 13; cuid456 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Homecoming, Miscellaneous, undated; cuid457 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Homecoming and Polytech Bowl, 1960s; cuid458 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Honor Roll, undated; cuid459 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Junior/Senior Prom, 1955; cuid460 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Junior-Sophomore Conference, 1967-1968; cuid461 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Military Programs- ASTP, 1940s; cuid462 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - ASTP and Training Corps negatives, 1917, 1943; cuid463 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Military Programs- ASTP & ROTC, undated; cuid464 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Military Programs- ROTC, undated; cuid465 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Military Programs- ROTC, 1950s; cuid466 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Military Programs- ROTC, 1950s - 1960s; cuid467 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Military Programs- ROTC, 1950s -1960s; cuid468 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Military Programs- ROTC Summer Camp, 1956-1960; cuid469 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Military Programs- ROTC, 1952-1964, cuid470 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Military Programs- ROTC, undated, cuid471 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Military Programs- ROTC Negatives, undated; cuid472 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Military Programs- SATC Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute OVERSIZE, undated; cuid473 (Box 23)
    - Military Science Slides, Undated; cuid474 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Music, Instrumental, undated; cuid475 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Open House, 1968; cuid476 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Paper Airplane Competition, 1997 November 4; cuid477 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Portraits of Students, undated; cuid478 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Poly Pride Week, 1998; cuid479 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Poly Pride Day 2001, 2001 April 11; cuid480 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Poly Pride Day 2002, 2002 April 17; cuid481 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Poly Pride Day 2003, 2003 April 30; cuid482 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Poly Sports Day/Soccer Tournament, 2003 September 13; cuid483 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Polytechnic Theater, undated; cuid484 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Robotics Competition 2001, 2001 December 10; cuid485 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Robotics Competition 2002, 2002 April 01; cuid486 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Rock Climbing, 1996; cuid487 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Scholarship Students, undated; cuid488 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Student-Faculty Groups, undated; cuid489 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Students, 1960s, cuid490 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Student Life, circa 1960; cuid491 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Student Life, 1920s - 1970s; cuid492 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Student Life- Long Island Campus, Farmingdale, 1993; cuid493 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Student Fund Loan Dance, 1959; cuid494 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Student Mixer, 1982; cuid495 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Students' Dance, 1950s; cuid496 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Students and Faculty, undated; cuid497 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Students and Professors in Labs, 1940-1949; cuid498 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Students in Livingston Building, circa 1952; cuid499 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Students in 333 Jay Street, 1960s -1970s; cuid500 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Students on Campus, 1980s; cuid501 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Students on Campus and in Labs, undated; cuid502 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Students in Computer Lab, undated; cuid503 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Students in Classrooms, 1940-1960; cuid504 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Students in Classrooms, 1960s - 1970s; cuid505 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Students in Classrooms, undated; cuid506 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Students in Classes, 1959; undated; cuid507 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Students in Dibner Building, 1990s; cuid508 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Students in Labs, undated; cuid509 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Students in Lounges, undated; cuid510 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Students in Microprocessor Lab, undated; cuid511 (Box 13A, Folder 1)
    - Student Awards, 1950s - 1980s; cuid512 (Box 13A, Folder 2)
    - Women at Poly, 1940s - 1960s; cuid513 (Box 13A, Folder 3)
    - General Student Life OVERSIZE, circa 1960; cuid514 (Box 23)
  - Subseries C: Clubs and Activities
    - Aero Club, 1940s; cuid515 (Box 13A, Folder 4)
    - Association of Latin America, undated; cuid516 (Box 13A, Folder 5)
    - Chess Club, undated; cuid517 (Box 13A, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1935 club photos, cuid518 (Box 13A, Folder 7)
    - Club Day, 1996; cuid519 (Box 13A, Folder 8)
    - Concrete Canoe, undated; cuid520 (Box 13A, Folder 9)
    - Glee Club, 1941-1955; cuid521 (Box 13A, Folder 10)
    - Grad Pre-Doctoral Group, 1967 Summer; cuid522 (Box 13A, Folder 11)
    - Physics Club, circa 1980; cuid523 (Box 13A, Folder 12)
    - Photo Club, circa 1955; cuid524 (Box 13A, Folder 13)
    - Poly Chem Society, 1935; cuid525 (Box 13A, Folder 14)
    - Polywog Staff, 1951; cuid526 (Box 13A, Folder 15)
    - Radio Club, undated; cuid527 (Box 13A, Folder 16)
    - Senior Gift Committee, 1996-1997; cuid528 (Box 13A, Folder 17)
    - Student Representatives, undated; cuid529 (Box 13A, Folder 18)
    - Women's Club, 1956-1961; cuid530 (Box 13A, Folder 19)
    - Women in Technology, 1994-1997; cuid531 (Box 13A, Folder 20)
  - Subseries D: Fraternities
    - Alpha Phi Delta, 1921-1952; cuid532 (Box 13A, Folder 21)
    - Alpha Phi Omega, undated; cuid533 (Box 13A, Folder 22)
    - Early Fraternities, 1880-1956; cuid534 (Box 13A, Folder 23)
    - Freshman Roundup 1954, cuid535 (Box 13A, Folder 24)
    - Freshman Roundup 1956, cuid536 (Box 13A, Folder 25)
    - Freshman Roundup 1963-1964, cuid537 (Box 13B, Folder 1)
    - Freshman Roundup 1964-1965, cuid538 (Box 13B, Folder 2)
    - Freshman Roundup 1965-1966, cuid539 (Box 13B, Folder 3)
    - Freshman Roundup 1966-1967, cuid540 (Box 13B, Folder 4)
    - Freshman Roundup 1968-1969, cuid541 (Box 13B, Folder 5)
    - Freshman Roundup 1973, cuid542 (Box 13B, Folder 6)
    - Pi Tau Sigma, 1956-1960; cuid543 (Box 13B, Folder 7)
    - Smokers, 1950-1957; cuid544 (Box 13B, Folder 8)
    - Zeta Beta Tau, 1954; cuid545 (Box 13B, Folder 9)
    - Sigma Psi (Oversize), Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Series VI: Alumni
  - Subseries A: General Alumni
    - Alumni 1920s-1930s, 1920-1939; cuid546 (Box 13B, Folder 10)
    - Alumni, undated; cuid547 (Box 13B, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Wall, undated; cuid548 (Box 13B, Folder 12)
    - Founder's Wall, undated; cuid549 (Box 13B, Folder 13)
  - Subseries B: Alumni Association
    - Alumni Association, 1983; undated; cuid550 (Box 13B, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Association, 1964-1967; cuid551 (Box 13B, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Association, circa 1900 - 1970s; cuid552 (Box 13B, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Association Homecoming, 1968; cuid553 (Box 13B, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Association Events, 1950s; cuid554 (Box 13B, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting 1970, cuid555 (Box 13B, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting 1971, cuid556 (Box 13B, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting 1973-1974, cuid557 (Box 13B, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting 2000, 2000 June 6; cuid558 (Box 13C, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Chapter Meetings, 2001; cuid559 (Box 13C, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Meeting, Nassau-Suffolk Section, 1964 June 6; cuid560 (Box 13C, Folder 3)
    - Mohawk Valley Section, 1950-1954; cuid561 (Box 13C, Folder 4)
    - Sections, P.S.L.I., 1960s; cuid562 (Box 13C, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Alumni Events
    - Annual Banquets & Dinners, 1967-1982; cuid563 (Box 13C, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Dinner 1949, cuid564 (Box 13C, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Dinner 1991, cuid565 (Box 13C, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Alumni Dinner, 1987 September; cuid566 (Box 13C, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Banquet 1943, cuid567 (Box 13C, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Banquet 1952, cuid568 (Box 13C, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Banquet 1953, cuid569 (Box 13C, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Banquet 1954, cuid570 (Box 13C, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Banquet 1955, cuid571 (Box 13C, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Day & Banquet 1956, cuid572 (Box 13C, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Banquet 1957, cuid573 (Box 13C, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Banquet 1958, cuid574 (Box 13C, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Banquet 1959, cuid575 (Box 13C, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Banquet 1960, cuid576 (Box 13C, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Banquet 1963, cuid577 (Box 13C, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Banquet 1964, 1964 February 15; cuid578 (Box 13C, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Banquet 1965, 1965 March 13; cuid579 (Box 13C, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Banquet 1966, 1966 March 12; cuid580 (Box 13C, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Banquet 1967, 1967 March 11; cuid581 (Box 13C, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Banquet 1968, cuid582 (Box 13C, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Banquet 1969, cuid583 (Box 13C, Folder 26)
    - Alumni Banquet 1970, cuid584 (Box 13C, Folder 27)
    - Alumni Banquet 1971, cuid585 (Box 13C, Folder 28)
    - Alumni Banquet 1972, cuid586 (Box 13C, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Banquet 1973, cuid587 (Box 13C, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Banquet 1974, cuid588 (Box 13C, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Banquet Miscellaneous, undated; cuid589 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Day 1957-1958, cuid590 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Day 1959, 1959 May 16; cuid591 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Day 1960, cuid592 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Day 1962-1963, cuid593 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Day 1964, 1964 May 9; cuid594 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Day 1965, 1965 March 22; cuid595 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Day 1966, 1966 April 30; cuid596 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Dance 1964- Long Island, cuid597 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Event 1994, 1994 February; cuid598 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Event 1996, cuid599 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Event 1996- Big Apple Chapter, cuid600 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Event 2001, 2001 June 5; cuid601 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Alumni NASA Tour, 1999; cuid602 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1998, 1998 November 12; cuid603 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1999, 1999 February 3; cuid604 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1999, 1999 February 3; cuid605 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1999, 1999 November 11; cuid606 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 2000, 2000 March 30; cuid607 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 2000, 2000 November 9; cuid608 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award 1996- Charles Hinkaty, 1996 June 6; cuid609 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award 1999- Herbert Henkel, 1999 September 27; cuid610 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award 2000- Dr. Tai-Lin Hsu, 2000 October; cuid611 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Distinctive Alumni, undated; cuid612 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Outstanding Alumni Lunch, undated; cuid613 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Outstanding Alumnus- Math Award, 1997 December 11; cuid614 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Student-Alumni Conference 1966, 1966 February 15; cuid615 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Student-Alumni Conference 1966, 1966 October 3; cuid616 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Student-Alumni Conference (ESO), undated; cuid617 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Subseries D: Alumni Leadership Seminar